# MOSTAFA JAD

#### • DETAILS •

+1 (416) 554-2532 m.mohamed.jad@gmail.com

# • SKILLS •

**JavaScript** 

Reactis

Nodejs

Express.js

NoSql Database

MySql

**AngularJS** 

Java

Docker

Git

AWS

Wordpress

• LINKS •

<u>GitHub</u>

#### • LANGUAGES •

English

Arabic

Spanish

# PROFILE

I have been programming since 2018. My main strength is web development. I'm a self-motivated professional who likes to solve problems. I merge my passion for usability and user experience with my technical knowledge to create cool digital experience.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Full Stack Developer at JadBeauty, Toronto (remote)

April 2020 — March 2021

- Design and implementation of web architecture.
- Pixel-perfect implementation of approved user interface.
- Design and deployment of database.
- Ensuring the entire stack is designed and built for speed and scalability.
- Design and construction of our REST API.

#### FrontEnd Developer at Just Eat it, Toronto

December 2019 — April 2020

- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications.
- Provided effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications.
- · Successfully worked well independently and within a team setting.
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements.

# FrontEnd Developer at GreenTrade, Toronto

September 2019 — December 2019

- Successfully contributed as a productive and positive team member to design, code, test, report, and debug operations.
- · Successfully managed front-end.
- Successfully identified, diagnosed, and fixed application problems,
- Helped to achieve a consistent look and visual theme across the application by promoting uniform fonts, formatting, images, and layout.
- Extended my knowledge in new standards, technologies, and trends in website and mobile application development.

# EDUCATION

Advanced Diploma of Software Engineer, Centennial College, Toronto September 2018 — April 2020

Bachelor of Business Information System, Arab Academy for Science & Technology, Alexandria

September 2012 — July 2016

# COURSES

Cloud Computing, Centennial College
December 2019 — April 2020

# **▼** REFERENCES

• References available upon request